- Oh, hey, guys. Where you headed?
- To the comic book store.
You're thinking,
"The comic book store on a Thursday?
(Sheldon:)Why, I've fallen down the rabbit hole
and into a land of madness."
What you have failed to take into account is
that this is Anything Can Happen Thursday.
(Penny:)You got me.
Oh, hey, could you pick me up
a few comics for my nephew's birthday?
No, I think you mean comic books.
Comics are feeble attempts at humor...
(Sheldon:)...featuring talking babies
and anthropomorphized pets...
(Sheldon:)...found traditionally
in the optimistically named "funny pages."
Leonard, pick me up comics
for my nephew's birthday?
- Sure. What does he like?
- I don't know, just pick out anything.
(Sheldon:)Just pick out anything?
Maybe we can pick out a new suit for him
without knowing his size...
(Sheldon:)...or pick out his career
without knowing his aptitude...
(Sheldon:)...or pick out a new breakfast cereal
without knowing his fiber requirements...
(Sheldon:)...or his feelings
about little marshmallows.